backstreets.com 2018-06-20

# Backstreets.com: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To send periodic emails  

> The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of the BTX message boards on our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their User Control Panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on August 28, 2013

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.backstreets.com  
1818 MLK Jr Blvd #300  
Chapel Hill, NC 27514  
USA  
editor@backstreets.com

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to [Zendesk](http://www.rhinosupport.com/zendesk.htm) and save!

|  |  |    

---  
  
\- About us  
Privacy Policy  
\- Contact Us  
  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
Join the Backstreets Email List  
Email:    
  
|  |   
| 

LIMITED EDITION SPRINGSTEEN PRINT  
****Outtake from the _Wild & _**_**innocent**_ **sessions by the late David Gahr, 8x10 fine art print in an edition of 300**

A rare opportunity to own an original Gahr print without breaking the bank, exclusively as part of this [Book + Print Set](http://www.backstreets.com/Merchant2/merchant.mvc?Screen=PROD&Product_Code=BKGAHRLTDED&Category_Code=001) from Backstreet Records

The [David Gahr book](http://www.backstreets.com/Merchant2/merchant.mvc?Screen=PROD&Product_Code=BKGAHR&Category_Code=001) from Rizzoli, a wonderful collection of Springsteen photos signed by editor Chris Murray, is also available separately.

**Read our interview with Chris Murry here**

Backstreet Records is the mailorder division of Backstreets, delivering Springsteen merchandise to fans for more than 25 years. We carry numerous collectibles, tour shirts, books, magazines, and imported CDs and records. **  
The world's best selection of Springsteen collectibles, all available by mail.**

**#91 IS HERE!  
**Our massive new issue honors a very Big Man. More than half of the 116-page, perfect bound _Backstreets_ #91 is a tribute to the life and music of... do we have to say his name?

**Full contents list  
  
---
